<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.5">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2019-04-18T15:48:37+03:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Mindstream today</title><subtitle>The blog is about homemade R&amp;D in computer science for enthusiasts.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Topics overview #1.</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/digest/2019/04/18/topics-overview-1.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Topics overview #1." /><published>2019-04-18T14:19:41+03:00</published><updated>2019-04-18T14:19:41+03:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/digest/2019/04/18/topics-overview-1</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/digest/2019/04/18/topics-overview-1.html">&lt;p&gt;Hi, everyone!
I have wanted to write an article for the blog for a long time. I have two incomplete notes. I can wait, again and again, but decided to start it with a short overview of the following themes:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The Iron bank stories - part 1: How to make an application for payments analysis and cash back calculation. I’m going to use Apache Ignite instead of Elasticsearch.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;I’m going to publish Kafka tasks from Joker conf. The tasks were prepared for the Alfabank exhibition stand.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Travel notes from battlefields of a new job.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The scalable world for a MMORPG - I’m going to make a distributed server for the old game Linage2.
These are my plans. If you have good topics, feel free to send them. See you.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Hi, everyone! I have wanted to write an article for the blog for a long time. I have two incomplete notes. I can wait, again and again, but decided to start it with a short overview of the following themes: The Iron bank stories - part 1: How to make an application for payments analysis and cash back calculation. I’m going to use Apache Ignite instead of Elasticsearch. I’m going to publish Kafka tasks from Joker conf. The tasks were prepared for the Alfabank exhibition stand. Travel notes from battlefields of a new job. The scalable world for a MMORPG - I’m going to make a distributed server for the old game Linage2. These are my plans. If you have good topics, feel free to send them. See you.</summary></entry></feed>